<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Get On My Level</string>
    <string name="rules_explanation"> Get On My Level is a guessing game between two teams. Each turn a team has a leader reveal the level shown hidden below that teams corresponding color to only themselves.The leader then gives a clue to indicate that level based on the corresponding prompt. The other team members will try to move the red bar to match the Level based on the click given by the leader. Before revealing the Level, the opposing team will have a chance to guess whether the original guess was either higher or lower than the actual level. After, press score and revealing the Level, if the team matches the Level shown they get 4 points for the green center, 3 points for the blue, and then 2 points for the outside yellow. If the Level is higher or lower and the opposing team guessed accurately they recieve one point. Then the next team chooses a new leader and prompt and play continues with the teams switching roles. The game ends after a team reaches 10 points with both teams playing the same amount of turns. With the team with more points at the end being declared the winner. In the case of a tie, play rounds where each team gets a turn until the tie is broken and the team with the most points is declared the winner.</string>
    <string name="rules_example">Example Turn: Team 1 selects Amanda to be the clue giver. Amanda gets the prompt least to most weird animal and sees the Level is towards the weird side. Knowing this Amanda states “Duck Billed Platypus”(a very weird animal), hides the Level, and gives her team the phone. Team 1 knows a Duck Billed Platypus is a weird animal and such moves the red selector bar towards the weird side. After deciding on a position they give the phone to team 2 who believes the Level is to the right(more weird) than where team 1 placed the selector. Therefore they switch the indicator to the higher position. They then give the phone back to Amanda who presses Score revealing the Level and automatically adding the points to each teams’ total. Team 2 then selects their clue giver and Amanda gives the phone to the new clue giver. The clue giver presses next turn and play continues the same way. </string>

</resources>
