<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Get On My Level</string>
    <string name="rules_summary">A Clue Giver is chosen to see the Level. The Clue Giver gives a short phrase or action
        to indicate the Level based on the prompt shown. The Clue Givers team members will attempt to place the Tuner at
        the same spot as the hidden Level. If they achieve this that team gets points. The opposing team can also score
        points during that turn. After the original team selects places the Tuner, the opposing team gets to guess
        whether the level is higher or lower than the original team believed. If correct, the opposing team scores a
        point. Play goes back and forth until 10 points is reached.
    </string>
    <string name="rules_example">Team 1 selects Amanda to be the Clue Giver. Amanda gets the prompt least to most weird
        animal and sees the Level is towards the weird side. Knowing this, Amanda states “Duck Billed Platypus”(a very
        weird animal), hides the Level, and gives her team the phone. Team 1 knows a Duck Billed Platypus is a weird
        animal and moves the Tuner towards the most weird side. After deciding on a position they give the phone to team
        2 who believes the Level is to the right(more weird) than where team 1 placed the Tuner. Therefore they select
        higher on the slider. They then give the phone back to Amanda who presses Score revealing the Level. The Tuner
        was in the Yellow on the least weird side of the Level. Therefore Team 1 gains 2 points and Team 2 gains 1
        point. Team 2 then selects their Clue Giver and Amanda gives the phone to the new Clue Giver. The Clue Giver
        presses next turn and play continues the same way.
    </string>
    <string name="level_explanation">This is the Level. If players are able to put the Tuner in the GREEN they receive 4
        points and the other team doesn’t even have a chance to score a point. In the BLUE, the team scores 3 points. In
        the YELLOW, the team scores 2 points.
    </string>
    <string name="tuner_explanation">This is the Tuner. Once the Level is hidden and the Clue Giver has given the clue
        the Clue Giver’s team moves the Tuner to match the Level they believe the Clue Giver was indicating.
    </string>
    <string name="new_prompt_explanation">Pressing the New Prompt Button will immediately change the prompt given and
        place the Level in a new spot along the gauge.
    </string>
    <string name="higher_lower_explanation">Set the slider to where the team thinks the Level is compared to where the
        opposing team placed the Tuner. If accurate, the team who set the slider gains 1 point.
    </string>
    <string name="score_button_explanation">Pressing the Score Button will reveal the Level and automatically add the
        points to each team’s total. (You can also manually edit each team’s total by clicking each team’s score)
    </string>
    <string name="next_turn_explanation">Pressing the Next Turn button will not score the current round and will
        immediately select a new random Level and Prompt as well as change the active team.
    </string>
    <string name="clue_giver_explanation">Each turn a team selects a Clue Giver who gets to see the Level and gives a
        clue based on the prompt to help the team place the Tuner on the Level. After giving the Clue the Clue Giver
        hides the Level and gives the phone to their team to place the Tuner.
    </string>
    <string name="clue_rules">The Clue can be a word, phrase, or action to address the Prompt but it cannot directly
        relate to the position of the Level. In other words, a Clue Giver can not say 75 as a Clue to indicate the Level
        is up 75% of the gauge.
    </string>
</resources>